Huh? Wait, what?
Sorry, are you okay?!
"Horimiya"
"Student Council Room"
"Everybody Loves Somebody"
Two, four, six, eight...
Thanks for picking these up for me.
Must be tough handling everything by yourself.
I don't do it all.
Remi and Sengoku-kun handle
the things they're able to handle.
Remi always opens this window for us,
so we get this nice breeze.
It's kind of cool how you work this hard,
even when nobody's looking.
Wait, are you talking about me?
Yeah.
You good with those papers?
Huh? Yeah, I'll be fine.
Thanks for the help, Ishikawa-kun.
Here.
This for me?
We were supposed to head
home together, but you didn't show.
So Hori-san...
Ugh, you must be dying of heat!
Promise me you'll take your
jacket off when you walk home!
Here, I got some frozen treats.
Have one with Toru when he gets here.
...gave me these. Apparently they were half off.
I see, they're from Hori.
"Juicy Melon"
How nice...
I can't have melon, dammit!
Huh?!
Hold it!
"Juicy Melon"
This is what you stopped me for?
Well, I can't eat two...
So I'm your garbage disposal?
Sorry.
Oh, Miyamura-kun, your tongue's turned white.
Maybe 'cause I'm eating this popsicle.
Let me see yours.
Whoa, it's green! Like, super green!
Glad you two are enjoying this.
I bet I'm the only one who didn't get anything.
Whoa, Ishikawa-kun, your tongue's kind of long.
Really?
It is long. Like a snake's.
I'll have to tell Remi
and Sakura about it later.
Could you not?!
Who's Sakura?
Sakura Kono. She's on the
student council with Remi and I.
Oh, the nerdy-looking girl!
Don't call her that.
Come to think of it, there are
a lot of girls on the council.
Sengoku's harem.
Hey! It's strictly business!
You get to use the A/C in the
council room as much as you want...
Like a spoiled king.
You have that much power, Prez?!
Don't make me out to be some villain.
Though, yes, the A/C is a special privilege.
You can swing by the student
council to cool off any time.
Huh?
You mean it?
"Student Council Room"
Rock, paper, scissors!
Ugh, I lost!
Hori-san and Mimyamura-kun have to go!
They swung by... and brought friends.
Oolong tea, orange juice, a cola... what else?
Strawberry milk.
Hey, are Hori-san and
Miyamura-kun really not dating?
Uh...
Who knows...
I feel like Ishikawa-kun would be
a way better match for Hori-san!
W-Wait, really?!
Cut it out. He just gave up on her.
Ishikawa-kun has a crush on Hori-san?
Yeah, sounds like it.
If you really want to be with Kyo-chan,
you'd better be one hell of a masochist.
Wait, what? Why? Where's this coming from?
Ishikawa-kun has a crush on Hori-san...
Oh, crap, the cola!
Who wanted that again?
They sure are taking their time getting drinks.
Wonder what they're up to?
I don't mean, like, they're
doing anything weird!
Yeah. What could they get up to
in the middle of the day at school?
So... what are they up to?
Sheesh, get it together!
Sorry...
See, look what you did.
I shouldn't have put it that way...
Don't worry. I bet Miyamura just
dropped the change or something.
"Psychic"
Don't worry. I bet Miyamura just
dropped the change or something.
Yoshikawa's kindness deserves to
be put in the class log for posterity.
Good thing I'm class leader today.
Don't fill the classroom log with useless crap.
Stop messing around with my hair!
Messing around...
Hey, sorry for the wait!
We would've been back sooner.
Hey, thanks! Got my cola?
I'm really sorry.
Huh? For what?
Hori screwed me.
I'm really sorry to do
this to you, Ishikawa-kun.
--Stop! I don't want to hear it! Please, don't!
--Wait, what?
--What happened?
--Stop! I don't want to hear it! Please, don't!
He was holding Toru's soda when...
Oh, damn, that really sucks!
If I were you, I'd be going after
the guy who did me like that!
Yeah, Sengoku-kun!
That's how a real man handles it!
Aw, man.
Yoshikawa?
You've got a bunch of pens, right?
Could you stab me in the arm with one?
Whoa! Why? Just cause you
got screwed out of a drink?
Yeah, c'mon, Ishikawa-kun.
I didn't mean to. It, like, just... happened.
Yeah, one thing lead to another.
I should've tried to stop it before it happened,
but the deed is done.
What's done is done! It's all good.
It's not good at all!
Ugh, c'mon, it's just a soda.
Wait... soda?
Why's it exploding?! Dammit, Miyamura!
My hands are all sticky...
--Now we gotta clean the floor. Got any rags?
--Miyamura-kun dropped your soda.
Man, is that all? I got all worried for nothing.
Here.
Thanks, Kono-san.
You're welcome.
Sorry the A/C's broken.
It's okay, I don't mind the heat.
Though at night, I'll sleep without clothes on.
Ugh, I should just study in the
student council room next time...
Wait, you sleep naked?!
Huh?! I mean, I wear underwear!
I just thought that was normal... Shoot...
Come to think of it, he doesn't
get embarrassed about undressing.
Wait, was I supposed to get
embarrassed when he undressed?!
Ugh, just thinking about it
makes me feel embarrassed...
Hey, Miyamura, can I see your tattoos?
Sure.
Don't start stripping!
Huh?!
All I asked was to see them
and you just start stripping?!
You didn't even ask why,
you just stripped! You're scaring me!
Your shouting is way scarier, Hori-san...
You're just cool with
stripping in front of people?
Huh? I mean, you know what it looks like, so...
What about if you stripped in front of Toru?
Well, yeah, but he knows
about the tattoos and stuff.
If Toru stripped in front of you,
would you get flustered?
I guess it depends on the situation.
So that means--
Stop!
Hold on, Hori-san.
Why are you asking me all this?
'Cause you don't seem to
get flustered about anything.
I was wondering what would get you flustered.
Like, I haven't really seen
you get embarrassed or blush...
I'm always the one
freaking out about stuff, right?
I blush super easily...
Uh-huh.
Oh, God! He's totally creeped out!
Wait, was I supposed to be embarrassed just now?
Okay, let's try it again!
What's the point?!
Besides, something's off.
I mean, it is hot.
Going shirtless would feel better.
So you are hot!
Hey, Hori-san, do you really think
I've never gotten flustered, ever?
W-Well, kind of. Like a teeny bit.
S-So not long ago, I ran into
a friend from middle school.
A friend?
Miyamura?
Shindo?
Damn, man, I'm jealous!
You're finally growin' up on me.
Wait, what?
Don't play coy with me, bro!
You mean me being a senior in high school now?
Heard you missed too
many days and got held back.
"Got Held Back"
Heard you missed too
many days and got held back.
"Got Held Back"
That's not what I mean, you moron!
I'm talking about that girlfriend
you're always walking around with!
Huh?! Sh-She's not my girlfriend!
C'mon, like I believe that.
I don't mind the joke, but Hori-san would.
So her name's Hori-san, huh?
You don't call your
girlfriend by her first name?
I-I totally do...
I blurted it out in the moment...
Wow.
Sorry. I thought I'd be fine with
him thinking you're my girlfriend,
but it still got me all flustered...
Oh, but don't worry, I'll tell him
right now that we're not dating.
Uh-huh.
I mean, you don't have to tell him we aren't...
Speak of the devil! It's my friend!
He just texted me...
What's that look for?
Ooh, he sent a picture. Lemme see!
C'mon, I wanna see!
One moment, please.
Don't get all polite on me!
C'mon, please?
"I got me a girlfriend! Cute, isn't she? I told her
we're gonna do a double date sometime!
Don't forget to use protection, wink wink!"
What is that moron thinking?!
"I got me a girlfriend! Cute, isn't she? I told her
we're gonna do a double date sometime!
Don't forget to use protection, wink wink!"
--C'mon. Are you listening? C'mon, Miyamura...
"Don't forget to use protection, wink wink!"
--Like hell I'm letting you see that!
--C'mon. Are you listening? C'mon, Miyamura...
Whoa! Volume!
Aaaand delete.
I've never seen you this
worked up before, Miyamura.
Huh? Oh, no, it's just 'cause he's such a moron.
--Like, for real...
--Hello? Oh, sup, Miyamura?
Piss off!
Is that how you always talk to
your friends from middle school?
Kinda.
I thought Miyamura was the
kind of guy who never god mad.
Why don't you try that
kind of reaction with Toru?
Maybe once we get to be better friends.
He's shy about the weirdest stuff.
You guys are pretty good friends
already though, yeah?
Y-You really think so?
Well, that's creepy.
There's so much I don't know about Miyamura.
I wonder what he was like in middle school...
Mmkay, I got that, and that...
Am I coming down with a cold?
Is it because I blasted
the A/C after it was fixed?
--No way, only morons catch colds
in the summer. I can't be sick.
--Hey, Hori-san!
--No way, only morons catch colds
in the summer. I can't be sick.
Who're you?
Wait, their new song's out?
Yeah, I borrowed the CD from Shu.
Apparently it came out last week.
Maybe I'll ask to borrow it, too.
The vocals are awesome...
Huh? Isn't that Hori?
Is that guy hitting on her?
Wait, Hori-sa...
Hey, Hori--
What the hell are you doing, Shindo?!
--Hey, Miyamura! What a coinkidink!
--He punched him without a second thought!
Shut up!
I've been your friend for forever!
You should at least introduce me!
Koichi Shindo, second year,
went to my school. There.
Sounds like how you'd find him on Google...
You know this guy, Miyamura?
Huh? Nope.
You just said he went to your school.
Wait, second year?
Yup. I'm repeating the grade.
So he's...
An idiot. It's 'cause he's stupid.
Yeah, but I'm at Yasaka! You're so mean.
"Hasaka High = Best School in the City
AKA Pachi High."
Yeah, but I'm at Yasaka! You're so mean.
"Hasaka High = Best School in the City
AKA Pachi High."
Pachi High?!
Still wish I could've gone to Katagiri with you.
What? Why?
'Cause you seem to be having a good time there.
Though maybe 'cause of your girlfriend.
I told you, we're not like that!
C'mon, don't be shy!
Shut your mouth!
Guys, if we're gonna stop and chat,
can we do it somewhere with A/C?
Oh! Why don't we hit up a restaurant, then?
C'mon, Shindo!
Aw, crap, that's the bell. We gotta
change classrooms, right? Let's go!
Hold up, Shindo!
Crap, I forgot my notebook. Go on without me.
You gonna go to class?
It starts in two minutes!
Sheesh, at least pick up your stuff!
Here.
Uhh, Yamamura?
Not my name.
Huh? What'd you say?
That's not my name.
Sorry! Your name's Yamamoto, right?
You're getting even colder.
Just kidding, Yamakawa!
"Yama" isn't in my name!
Kawada!
Now you're just trying all
the "Kawa" names! Come on!
--I haven't talked to a classmate
or raised my voice in so long...
--Wait, was there a "hashi" in your name?
--I haven't talked to a classmate
or raised my voice in so long...
--No!
--I haven't talked to a classmate
or raised my voice in so long...
...that it feels weird to be doing it now.
Miyamura!
Hey, I was drinking that!
C'mon, lemme have a sip.
Oh, hey, did you catch the concert
on TV last night? The Osaka one!
Yeah, I did! It was awesome.
Right? The lighting and stuff were so cool!
I wanna go to a concert someday...
Shindo, you've been hanging out
with Miyamura a lot lately, huh?
Yeah, what about it?
You should probably stop, dude.
He's all gloomy and depressing.
And he has tons of piercings and shit.
I've seen 'em.
When that kind of guy loses his temper,
it's bad news for everyone.
Shindo, you gotta--
Who do you think made him get that way?
I know you guys are just mad
'cause you think he stole me from you.
Don't worry, we'll hang out again sometime.
--Shindo changed my whole
middle school experience.
--Do you know about the new place
that opened up over here?
--Shindo changed my whole
middle school experience.
--Yeah, though I haven't been yet.
--Shindo changed my whole
middle school experience.
You guys are paying, right?
--What?!
--And the person who's changed
my high school experience...
--What?!
--And the person who's changed
my high school experience...
You seem to be having a good time there.
C'mon, Miyamura!
...has got to be Hori-san.
Whoa! Your fever's really high!
And Mom already went to work...
Oh, no...
Where're you going?
School.
But you have a fever! You should rest!
I can't be sick. Only morons
catch colds in the summer.
So I can't have a cold.
You totally do, though.
I gotta g...
C'mon, Sota.
You're gonna stay home and rest today!
I gotta go to school,
so don't die while I'm gone!
I'm not gonna die. Have a good day at school.
Thanks, feel better!
Sota sure is growing up quick...
Kyoko...
I'm so sorry, Kyoko,
but there's an emergency at work.
I wish I could stay, but I have to go.
Mama, I...
Ugh, my nose is all stuffed up...
Hori-san, do you need a towel?
Yeah, thanks.
No prob.
Let me know when you need a dry one.
I also brought you a sports drink.
Am I hallucinating? Why're you here, Miyamura?
Huh?
Sota called me this morning saying
you "might die," so I swung by.
"Cold Meds"
Sota called me this morning saying
you "might die," so I swung by.
Okay.
Did you get dressed for school
this morning? How high's your fever?
Thirty-ei...
Thirty, uh, seven... around there.
Did you take any cold meds?
Yeah, not long ago.
Okay then. Good.
You should change out of your uniform...
Hori-san!
Wait... what?!
Huh?
Where are you going?
U-Uh, to get you a drink?
Where are you going?!
Hori-san, for real, though,
you should go lie down.
Where... are you going?
Kyoko, you're always so
good at toughing things out...
I know I shouldn't take
advantage of that. I'm sorry.
It's okay. Dad's not around right
now, and work's rough on you.
I'm not a little kid anymore.
I'll be fine.
Have a good day at work, Mom!
Why?
Why are you never, ever, ever here?!
Where are you going?!
Hori-san, instead of "where are you going,"
do you mean, "please don't go"?
Where are you going?
I'm not going anywhere.
Until you say you don't need me here anymore,
or get sick and tired of looking at my face,
or tell me to buzz off,
I'm going to stay right here.
Mmkay.
Make sure you drink some
water later though, okay?
Okay, I'm heading out.
I called your mom and told
Ishikawa-kun to tell school you're sick.
Also,
I'm in love with you, Hori-san.
Have been for a while now.
There're drinks and food in the fridge.
If you need anything, call or
text me. I'll come right over.
Huh? What? What did he just say?!
I'm so shocked, my fever's
practically disappeared!
Why? Why'd he tell me in the
middle of all that boring stuff!?
He knew I was awake
when he said all that, right?!
I don't get it. I need to know if he said it!
But I don't want to make him say it again!
If...
If I pretend I didn't hear it,
maybe we can stay like this
for a little while longer...
"I Can't Say It Out Loud"